

# **CONTACTS**

- ♠ Dnipro, Ukraine.
- & Tel. +380 93 726-28-35
- @ dev.byartem.com

## LANGUAGES

ENGLISH intermediate / B1

**POLISH** elementary / A1

UKRAINIAN / RUSSIAN native

SKILL Technical:	beginner elementary medium strong excellent
HTML5 / CSS3	
Bootstrap / Materialize	
LESS	
JavaScript (ES5 / ES6)	
jQuery	
Design tools:	
PhotoShop	
Lightroom	
Sketch app.	
Additional:	
Teamwork	
Team Management	
Project Management	
Problem solving	
Car driving	

Office solutions

# ARTEM BLOSCHINSKY

Objective junior front-end developer

## ABOUT ME



I was born in Dnipro, 32 years' old, not married.

Over 10 years' of working experience in different business areas, such as: foodstuff, hard-truck transport logistics, photography, design, digital printing. Have a practical understanding of business needs within B2B and B2C fields. Teamwork experience in such countries as Poland, Greece, Moldova & Russia.

Computers, networks & software development inspire and enjoy me from the school time. And my engineering education is a good technical background for employment.

My hobbies are photography, traveling by car, cycling, post crossing. I have B category driving license, strong driving skills, and long term opened Schengen visa.

## WORK EXPERIENCE



PP KUCHMENKO / Purchase & transportation deputy director

KAMENEC-PODOLSKY / FEBRUARY 2012 - MAY 2016

Work with suppliers selection and organization of the goods delivery quality control prob

Work with suppliers, selection and organization of the goods delivery, quality control, problem solving, transport & logistics management, quality control of vehicles and drivers.

#### SELF EMPLOYED PHOTOGRAPHER

UKRAINE / SEPTEMBER 2009 - PRESENT TIME

Photo shooting, photo editing, promotion, work with clients.

#### **RASTUDIO** / prepress, designer, retoucher.

DNIPRO / SEPTEMBER 2003 - SEPTEMBER 2009

Work with customers, preparation photographs for large-format printing, photographic design, retouching and restoration of photographs.

## **EDUCATION**



**2017-PRESENT TIME** 

SPALAH IT-SCHOOL

JavaScript software development

2016-2017

**HTMLACADEMY** 

Web development (HTML & CSS)

2002-2007

#### NATIONAL MINING UNIVERSITY

Information security of computer systems and networks.